sexiluv.com 2010-01-03

# SexiLuv.com - Sexy & romantic images & comments for MySpace, Orkut, Hi5, Friendster, Facebook - Latino & Portuguese Comments

**

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

_SexiLuv.com Privacy Policy_

This privacy statement was developed to demonstrate our firm and continuous commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name & IP Address, but not the e-mail address of the user. 

We do not collect any information about our visitor's email or referring domain. For visitors on our website we collect Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. 

With respect to cookies: We set cookies to store certain user preferences such as your favorite categories, or other feature choices. Additionally, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on browsers, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on the site. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at this page from time to time. 

For futher information contact us at: webmaster at sexiluv dot com. 

**
